

CONTACT

650.889.6714 richa.naniwadekar@gmail.com https://nricha.github.io linkedin.com/in/richa-naniwadekar

TOOLS

ADOBE CREATIVE SUITE:

Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, After Effects (basic)

APP AND WEB DESIGN SOFTWARE:

Sketch, Invision, Flinto, Wordpress, Weebly, Canva

PRESENTATION SOFTWARE:

PowerPoint and Keynote

SKILLS

UI/UX Design
User Research
User Surveys, and Interviews
User Personas
Wireframing and creating mockups
Usability and Preference Testing
Prototyping and animating
Responsive web & app design
Basic HTML/CSS knowledge
Microsoft Office Suite
Windows and Mac OS X
Digital Photography

EDUCATION

UI DESIGN CERTIFICATE • 2018 - 2019 CareerFoundry

A.A IN GRAPHIC DESIGN • 2014 - 2017De Anza Community College

POST GRADUATE CERTIFICATE IN
TRAVEL AND TOURISM • 2007 - 2008
Sophia Polytechnic, Mumbai

BACHELORS IN MASS MEDIA, ADVERTISING • 2004 - 2007 University of Mumbai

RICHA NANIWADEKAR

VISUAL AND UI DESIGNER

SUMMARY

A Visual and UI designer with over 6 years of combined experience in sales, marketing, and design. Brings to the table a keen eye for detail, a talent for dealing with demanding clients and stakeholders, and a track record of solving problems creatively.

WORK EXPERIENCE

GRAPHIC DESIGNER • Feb, 2018 - Present

YMCA OF SILICON VALLEY

- Producing compelling print-ready and digital graphics for various marketing purposes while adhering to the brand guidelines.
- Attending to requests for flyers, posters, digital banners, event materials, t-shirt designs, brochures, and other marketing materials, and delivering them on time.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER • Aug, 2017 - June, 2018 10 BOOKS A HOME

- Created and led the design of digital and print assets for marketing, research, and fundraising purposes as the sole graphic and visual designer
- Developed digital images, infographics, flyers, illustrations, presentation decks, brochures, social media content, and website-related material.
- Updated website content using Weebly.

VOLUNTEER ILLUSTRATOR • Aug, 2013 - Apr, 2014 BAY AREA OLDER ADULTS

- Created artwork for a yet-to-be-published e-book. Designed the e-book cover, illustrated/sketched maps and events corresponding to the events in the book.

SR. SALES MANAGER AND TOUR MANAGER • Aug, 2009 - Sept, 2012 SACHIN TOURS AND TRAVELS LTD

- Built and managed a travel sales team from the ground up. Collaborated with stakeholders, trained, and led a sales team to design customized itineraries, travel quotes and vouchers. The department grew to four other team members.
- Solo-led 40-spassenger group tours across Southeast Asia and the United States.

JR. WEB MARKETING EXECUTIVE • Aug, 2008 - May, 2009 ORBIT CORPORATE AND LEISURE TRAVELS (I) PVT. LTD

- Designed web marketing and digital marketing materials like direct emails.
- Worked on maintaining and refreshing website content for online travel packages and other website related materials.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Juror's Award for Best Poster Design at 2017 De Anza College Student Art Show **Served as a program advisor** for De Anza College's Graphic and Interactive Design Department